这是什么
What is this?
-哦哦  我知道  -等一下
- Ooh ooh! I know!  - Wait.
-我想让盖比来回答  -呀
- I want Gabe to answer.  - Aw.
嗯  这是个盘子
Uh... It's a plate.
错
Wrong.
哇哦  我真上了一课 不该那么骄傲
Whoa. That'll teach me to get cocky.
这是个脏盘子  你应该把它放到洗碗机里面
It's a dirty plate, which you were supposed to put in the dishwasher.
快点  能有多难
Now come on! How easy is that?
既然那么简单  为啥你不干
If it's so easy, why didn't you do it?
所有盘子都收拾干净了  就一个在你手上
Now the plate's all the way out here and that one's on you.
你知道吗  先生
You know what, Mister?
你刚刚给自己买了一张本周院子拔草活的票
You just bought yourself a ticket to a weekend of yard work.
收拾盘子去
Take care of the plate.
他最近老是找我茬
He's really been on my case lately.
我都不知道该怎么办了
I don't know what to do about it.
恩
Well...
你本可以把盘子放进洗碗机里面
You could put that plate in the dishwasher.
是啊  那他就说了算了
Yeah, but then he wins.
老弟  你应该跟我学学
Brother man, you should do what I did.
搬出去住
Get your own apartment.
老兄  我才十三岁
Dude, I'm 13.
恩  那咱们还是说说盘子的事儿吧
Well, then we're back to the plate.
啊  嘿
Oh hey!
我有个主意  我这个礼拜上你家住好不
I got an idea. How about I come stay at your place this weekend?
哦  好啊  行  为啥不呢  埃米特出城了  应该没问题
Oh, yeah, sure. Why not? Emmett's out of town. Should be fun.
-嘿  我能带上杰克吗  -行
- Hey, can I bring Jake? - Sure.
好吧  这太棒了
All right, this is great.
既然我不在这里了  我就没必要拔院子里的草了
Since I'm not here, I don't have to do yard work.
这样的话猜猜谁赢了
And then guess who wins?
-我赢了  是是  不  我知道  我只是
- I do.  - Yeah yeah... No, I know. I was just...
整个盘子事件让我有点发毛
Got nervous after the whole plate thing.
■
本字幕由★迪幻字幕组★为您奉献
欢迎登录www.Deefun.com
生活搞得一团糟
<i>Today's all burnt toast </i>
就要迟到  爸爸在叫
<i>Running late, and dad jokes</i>
我左脚的鞋子有没有人看到
<i>"Has anybody seen my left shoe?"</i>
■
翻译： Crazy王
我闭上眼  咬口早餐
<i>I close my eyes, take a bite</i>
跳上车子  放声大笑
<i>Grab a ride, laugh out loud</i>
哎呀  老爸  鞋子就在房顶上
<i>There it is up on the roof.</i>
■
校订： Enpistu
我也曾这样生活  我已经顺利走过
<i>I've been there, I've survived</i>
所以听取我的建议
<i>So just take my advice.</i>
■
后期： Enpistu  liloelva
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
世界有很多疯狂无奈
<i>Things are crazy</i>
可是我知道你会有美好将来
<i>But I know your future's bright.</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby</i>
不要怀疑
<i>There's no maybe</i>
一切终会如你所愿
<i>Everything turns out all right.</i>
生活有悲有喜
<i>Sure life is up and down.</i>
但是请相信我  坚持就有好结果
<i>But trust me, it comes back around.</i>
你会喜欢将来的你
<i>You're gonna love who  you turn out to be.</i>
宝贝  不要放弃
<i>Hang in there, baby.</i>
查莉成长日记  第三季第十六集
Good Luck Charlie  S03E16  Guys & Dolls
斯宾塞  你咋就不懂呢
Spencer, how are you not understanding this?
我只是 我只是没感觉有啥了不起的
I just... I just don't see what the big deal is.
好吧好吧  我再给你分析一下
Okay okay. Let me break this down one more time.
是这样  我刚在话剧课上表演完
So, I had just done my big performance in drama class.
然后  那个讨人厌的艾什利就走过来跟我说
And then, that horrible Ashley walks up to me and she says...
你好像演得很开心啊
"Looks like you're really having fun out there."
我还是没搞懂这有什么不妥
I still don't see why that's so bad.
她这是在侮辱我
She was totally insulting me!
可  通过说你玩得开心
But... By saying you had fun?
没错  那正是你演的很烂时  别人才这么说的
Yes, that's what you say when somebody's performance stinks.
这地球人都知道
Everybody knows that.
泰迪  我感觉你在无中生有
Teddy, it just seems like you're making a big deal out of nothing.
哦是吗  是吗
Oh yeah? Yeah?
好吧  我感觉你在有中生无
Well, it seems like you're making nothing out of a big deal!
是的  那就是我想说的
Yeah, that's what I meant to say.
好了
Okay.
谁把托比的玩具都扔到走廊里了
Who put all of Toby's stuffed animals on the porch?
盖比
Gabe.
啊
Aw.
她把初犯栽我身上了
She pinned her first crime on me.
-我该怎么办  -什么怎么办
- What am I gonna do about this?  - About what?
查莉  她老是不喜欢托比
Charlie. She still doesn't like Toby.
这都好几个月了  我还以为现在她都完事了呢
This has been going on for months. I thought she'd be over it by now.
老妈  这得慢慢来
Mom, some things take time.
我是说  我还是不喜欢查莉
I mean, I still don't like Charlie.
泰迪不喜欢我  PJ不喜欢泰迪
Teddy doesn't like me. PJ doesn't like Teddy.
这才叫家
It's what makes us a family.
盖比  这次我不想这样了
Gabe, I wanted this time to be different.
毕竟  托比将是我最后一个宝宝了
After all, Toby is gonna be my last baby.
是吗
Mm-hmm.
进来
Come on in.
-嗨  -嗨
- Hey. - Hey.
嗯  这就是你住的地方  嗯
So. This is where you live, huh?
是滴
Yep.
嗯  这还是比拔草强
Well, it's still beats doing yard work.
嘿  盖比他哥
Hey, Gabe's brother.
-还好吗  -嘿
- What's up? - Hey.
-杰克呢  -他有点事  所以
- What happened to Jake? - He was busy, so...
我叫了其他几个哥们  嗯嗯
I called a couple of other kids and, uh...
他们都来不了  所以
They weren't able to make it either, so...
我们有了洛根
Here's Logan.
他们总是最后才找我
I'm often the last choice.
查莉  我给你买了个礼物
Charlie, I bought you a present.
么么  可爱吧
Mm! Isn't it cute?
哦哦  拿着
Ohh. Here you go.
好了  首先我们要给他起个名字
Now, the first thing we need to do is name him.
好的  什么样的名字才适合男宝宝呢
Right, now what's a really good name for a sweet little baby boy?
哦  好了  比如乔比
Oh, well, there's... Joby...
或者是科比  或者是
Or Kobe, or...
-托比  -托比
- Toby. - Toby!
这是个好主意
That's a great idea.
好了妈咪要照顾妈咪的宝宝了  你要照顾你的宝宝了
So now when mommy's taking care of her baby you can take care of your baby.
我要把我的托比抱起来然后给他一个抱抱
I'm going to pick up my Toby and give him a hug.
你好  小宝贝
Hello, little man.
嗨
Hello.
哦哦  大大的拥抱  耶
Ooh, big hug. Yeah.
你要给你的托比一个大大的拥抱了
And you're gonna give your Toby a big hug.
哦
Oh.
老娘出马  宝刀未老
Mommy shoots...  She scores.
嘿  斯宾塞  鲜花  嗯哼
Hey, Spence. Flowers, huh?
耶  我太对不起泰迪了
Yeah. I really owe Teddy an apology.
对不起什么
For what?
我也不知道
I have no idea.
算你走运  我知道为啥  来  去我办公室
Luckily for you, I do. You know what? Step into my office.
好了  听着
Okay. Look.
她之所以对你不高兴是因为
The reason she got mad at you is that
你没有因为她的无是生非而不高兴
you didn't get upset about nothing.
是的  但那的确没有什么事 是吧
Yeah, but it was nothing, right?
恩 那当然是啥事都没有
Well, of course it was nothing.
-嗯  我知道你懂的  -是的
- Well, I mean you know that. - Yeah.
我懂
I know that.
我们在讨论女人这个物种
We're talking about the female of the species.
是吧  一种超级不讲道理的生物
Okay? A highly irrational creature.
算你走运  磨砺了20年之久的婚姻生涯  我也算个专家了
Fortunately for you, after 20 long years of marriage, I am kind of an expert.
好了  听着  关键在于
Okay. Look. The key...
你得让泰迪觉得你在乎那些
Is that you gotta let Teddy think that you care about...
没必要大惊小怪的事情
All this stuff that's not worth caring about.
听着  当她们再出现  像  像
Look, when they have an issue, like, like...
-像昨天泰迪出现的问题  -嗯嗯
- Like Teddy did yesterday... - Mm.
你要做的不是反应
You just don't react.
而是过度反应
You overreact.
-我该怎么做  -我教你  来
- So how do I do that? - I'll show you. Okay.
-来  你来做泰迪  -好的
- You know what, you be Teddy.   - Okay.
-我来做你  好了  -耶
- I'll be you. All right. - Yeah.
-对某件事情生个气  -好吧  嗯嗯
- Get mad about something. - Okay. Um.
我学校有个女生看不惯我的发型
A girl at school didn't like my hair.
什么
What?!
怎么可能有人不喜欢你的发型
How could someone not like your hair?!
-你的发型是最棒的  -嗯  嘿  冷静一下
- You have the best hair ever. - Well, hey, calm down.
不  我怎么能冷静下来  你知道吗  这  这
No, I can't! You know what? It just... It just...
这要气死我了  你看  你的发型是这么的棒
It just burns me because your hair is so awesome.
-感觉如何  -感觉你真的很在乎我的发型
- How do you feel? - Like you really care about my hair.
何止
And...
我根本不在乎
I couldn't care less.
哦  邓肯叔叔  这真是绝门了
Oh, Mr. Duncan. This is really good stuff.
是吧  嘿  你知道这招儿的绝门之处吗  屡试不爽啊
Isn't it? Hey, you know the beauty of this is, it works every time.
除了下次
Except the next time.
注意  来了个骑滑板的
Okay, here comes a skateboarder.
好了  准备
All right, wait for it.
准备
Wait for it.
扔
Now.
哦  爽
Oh yes!
哦  他抬头了  抬头了
Oh. Looking up. Looking up!
披萨到了
Pizza's here.
-嘿  你俩在做干啥  -扔水气球
- Hey, what are you guys doing?  - Dropping water balloons.
快点  该你了
Come on, it's your turn.
快点  来了两个老太太  快点
Quick. There's two old ladies coming. Come on.
你俩不能扔水气球
You guys cannot be dropping water balloons.
-嗯  为啥  -因为我在这住
- Well, why not?  - Because I live here.
并且我想一直在这住下去  拿帐篷做什么
And I want to keep living here. And what is with the tent?
我们要过夜
It's a sleepover.
没帐篷怎么过夜啊
You can't have a sleepover without a tent.
好吧  那么
All right, well.
拿走了
We'll take this.
嘿  伙计们  披萨是给我们所有人吃的
Hey, guys. That pizza's for all of us.
嘿  咱们来打几个恶作剧电话
Hey, let's make some prank phone calls.
哦  得了吧  恶作剧电话  你俩都13了
Oh, come on. Prank phone calls? You guys are 13 years old.
你真以为  等等
Are you really... Oh, hang on.
你好
Hello?
没有啊  我的屁屁没着火  你是谁啊
No my butt is not on fire. Who is this?
小子们  安静  我正在打电话呢
Boys, quiet. I'm on the phone.
泰迪  斯宾塞来了
Teddy, Spencer's here.
哦  谢了
Oh, thanks.
哦  等  等  让我说完
Oh, no no. You didn't let me finish.
斯宾塞在这儿  正在和你爸谈话
Spencer's here talking with your father.
谈什么
About what?
有意思了
That's the interesting part.
耶  我刚刚偶然听到鲍伯博士
Yeah. I just overheard Dr. Bob...
女性学教授
Professor of Womanology...
向斯宾塞传授对付我们女生的最佳策略
Explain to Spencer that the best way of handling us gals
就是假装关心那些没必要大惊小怪的事
is to pretend to care about stuff that isn't worth caring about.
是吗  好吧  我了解斯宾塞  他保证会说这太可笑了
Really? Well, if I know Spencer, he said that that was ridiculous.
呵呵  你不了解斯宾塞
Well, you don't know Spencer.
我记得他的原话是
I believe his exact words were...
这真绝门了  邓肯叔叔
"This is really good stuff, Mr. Duncan."
嗯
Huh.
那么  我得跟我家那小伙谈谈了
Well, I think I need to have a little chat with my fella.
别  别  别  别
No no no no.
这种事我们女生不通过交流来解决
We do not handle these things with communication.
喂喂  泰迪  咱们得报复一下
Come on, Teddy. We get revenge.
先杀斯宾塞
First on Spencer...
再斩鲍伯博士
Then on Dr. Bob.
哦  我发现家里出了位艾米博士
Oh, I see Dr. Amy's in the house.
可不是么
Mm-hmm.
并且她打算实施重磅炸弹计划
And she's about to administer 10 CC's of ba-bam.
喔
Oh!
嘿  伙计们  音量
Hey, guys? Volume.
哦  他说得对  咱把音量调大一点
Oh, he's right. Let's crank it up.
不是  音量调小
No. Turn it down.
-啥  -调小
- What? - Down.
我没法听见自己的思考了
I can't hear myself think.
谁都听不见你的思考
No one's ever heard you think.
你知道吗  到此为止  我受够你俩了
You know what? That is it. I have had enough of you two.
不许再玩电子游戏了
No more video games.
-啥  -不许玩电子游戏了
- What? - No more video games.
我在复习考试
I'm trying to study for a test.
-那我们怎么办  -我不管  只要不出声就行
- What are we supposed to do?  - I don't care, as long as it's quiet.
哥们  我记得你说过你哥挺有趣的
Man, I thought you said your brother was fun.
他曾经是的
He used to be.
在他变成老爸之前
Before he turned into dad.
你刚刚说什么  先生
What did you just say, Mister?
你现在连说话都像他了
Now you even sound like him.
你知道  我来这就是为了躲他  不是来陪一个少年版老爸
You know, I came over here to get away from him, not to be with dad junior.
我可不是少年版老爸
I am not dad junior.
并且你刚刚给自己买了张刷盘子的票
And you just bought yourself a ticket to doing the dishes.
-我们用的是纸盘子  -我要它们一尘不染
- We used paper plates. - And I want them spotless.
玛丽露  我应该当个儿童心理学专家
Mary Lou, I should be a child psychologist.
真的
Really.
我给查莉了一个娃娃托比  她很喜欢他
I gave Charlie a Toby doll and she loves it.
过不久她就会喜欢上真正的托比了
And pretty soon she'll feel the same way about the real Toby.
我要告诉你  这主意太妙了
I'm telling you, it's brilliant.
日后这招将被称为  邓肯杀手锏
One day it will simply be known as "the Duncan method."
我回头打给你
Let me call you back.
查莉
Charlie?
你是不是把垃圾桶错当成魔幻娃娃屋了
Did you mistake the trash can for a magical doll house?
没有
No.
我不是两岁小孩
I'm not two.
哦  查莉
Oh, Charlie.
你为什么不喜欢宝宝托比呢  他好喜欢你
Why don't you love baby Toby? He loves you so much.
-你怎么知道的  -他告诉我的
- How do you know? - Because he told me.
他不会说话
He can't talk.
或许会哦
Or can he?
你在看什么
What are you looking at?
是的  不  我知道我丢了收据  但我从来没穿过它们
Yes... No, I understand that I lost the receipt, but I never wore them,
所以为什么我不能给它们换回去
so why can't I take them back?
可  那愚蠢的政策
But that's a stupid policy!
算  算了
Nev... Never mind.
怎么了
What was that all about?
我买了双运动鞋但是尺寸不对
I bought these running shoes, but they were in the wrong size
现在那个破商店不让我退
and now the stupid store won't let me return them.
哦这样啊  你打算怎么办
Oh well. What are you gonna do?
我告诉你我要做什么
I'll tell you what I'm gonna do.
我要大发怒火
I'm gonna get angry!
他们怎敢如此待你
How dare they treat you like that?!
-什么  -难以置信
- What?  - I can't believe this.
哪个傻帽惹到你的
Who was the idiot you were dealing with?
嗯  我记得是个叫山姆的人
Uh, I think it was someone named Sam?
哦 山姆的大脑一定只有胡桃那么大
Oh, Sam must have a brain the size of a walnut.
斯宾塞  亲爱的  冷静一下
Spencer, honey. Just calm down.
不  我怎么能冷静下来  知道吗  气死我了这个山姆
No, I can't calm down, all right? Because I am so furious with this Sam!
这个山姆真让我恶心
I am disgusted by Sam.
你这么想我太高兴了
I am so glad you feel this way.
我去拿钥匙
I'm gonna get my keys.
等一下
Wait.
你拿钥匙做什么
What are you getting your keys for?
我们要去那家商店  你要给山姆
Because we are going down to that store and you're gonna give Sam
一点颜色瞧瞧
a piece of my mind!
这都发生什么事了
What just happened?
毫无头绪
I don't know.
我们已经进入了一个未知领域
We're in uncharted territory.
-我现在该怎么办  -我不知道
- What do I do now? - I don't know.
我们已进入了一个未知领域
We're in uncharted territory.
喂
Psst.
嘿  查莉
Hey, Charlie.
谁说话
Who said that?
是我  托比
It's me, Toby.
过来
Come here.
你能说话了
You can talk?
只跟你说
Just to you.
查莉
Charlie?
全家我最喜欢你
You're my favorite in the whole family.
-真的吗  -是的
- Really? - Yeah.
我爱你  查莉
I love you, Charlie.
你也爱我吗
Do you love me too?
是的
Yes.
那真是太
That is so...
棒滴
Goody.
记住  这是咱俩的小秘密
Now remember, this is our very special secret.
只有咱俩知道  别告诉别人
Just for us. Don't tell anyone.
好吗
Okay?
好的
Okay.
嗨  查莉
Hi, Charlie.
托比讲话了
Toby talks.
你知道吗  没必要大闹一场
You know, there's no reason to cause a scene.
我觉得我们只要当面表明观点就行了
I think we made our point just by showing up.
是的  嗨  我们想找一下山姆  有事
Yes, hi. We'd like to speak to Sam. We have a problem.
我是山姆
I'm Sam.
有什么事
What seems to be the problem?
没事
No problem.
但你刚刚说有事
But you just said there was a problem.
不  嗯  不  她说的
No, uh, no. She said it.
上啊  斯宾塞  你怎么跟我说的就怎么跟他说
Come on, Spencer. Tell him what you told me.
神耶  这谁能记得
Gosh. Who can remember?
他说你的大脑只有胡桃那么大
He said you have a brain the size of a walnut.
再说一遍
Excuse me?
嗯
Uh.
公平讲  我见过很多大胡桃哦
To be fair, I've seen some pretty large walnuts.
还有  他说你让他恶心
And... And he said that he was disgusted by you.
但那是我被怒气冲昏了头口不择言
But then I walked it back to just furious.
你还有什么想要说的没
Is there anything else you'd like to say to me
在我把你放到休息室之前
before I take you into the break room?
一个可以修理你的地方
Where I will break you.
啊  等一下  嗯  听着  那些话都不是我想说的
Ah, wait. Uh, look. I didn't mean any of the things I said.
是这样  我只是从他老爸那里学了点馊主意  那个  我太傻了
See, I took some bad advice from her father, and uh, I was really stupid.
并且我太抱歉了
And I am very sorry.
请不要修理我
Please don't break me.
-听够了吗  泰迪  -谢谢  山姆  我很满意
- Heard enough, Teddy? - Thanks, Sam. I'm good.
冷静  希望没太吓到你  小伙子
Cool. Hope I didn't scare you too much, little guy.
刚刚发生什么事了
What just happened?
哦  刚刚所发生的就是  我  一个女性
Oh, what just happened was I, the woman...
给你  这个傻帽  上了一节课
Taught you, the idiot, a lesson.
-这么说你全听到了  -我妈全听到了
- So you heard everything?  - My mom did.
哦
Oh.
听着  我答应你我再也不向你父亲讨教了
Look, I promise I'll never take advice from your father again.
大家最终都会这么做的
Everyone gets there eventually.
哦  嗯  再次谢谢你  山姆
Oh, uh, thanks again, Sam.
嘿  你俩怎么认识的
Hey, how do you guys know each other?
哦  他是我话剧社里的人  干得漂亮
Oh, he's in my community theater group. Great job.
谢谢  泰迪  还有你
Thanks, Teddy. And you...
看上去你演得很开心啊
Really looked like you were having fun out there.
好吧  受伤了
Well, that hurt.
她在这啊
There she is.
我一生的挚爱
The woman I love.
这些献给你
These are for you.
嗯嗯  什么事
Hmm. What's the occasion?
非要有理由吗
There has to be an occasion?
难道一个男人不能给他妻子买花仅仅是因为
Can't a man give the love of his life flowers just because?
知道鞋店的事了
Heard about the shoe store?
是的  我知道了
Yes, I did.
请收下这些花吧
Please accept the flowers.
嗯嗯  不要  谢谢了
Hmm. No thanks.
哦  别这样  亲爱的
Oh, come on, honey.
亲爱的
Honey.
别这样
Come on.
我教给斯宾塞的那些东西我一点都不信
I don't really believe any of that stuff that I was telling Spencer.
并且你知道吗  既然泰迪给斯宾塞上了节课
And you know what? Since Teddy taught him a lesson...
我看真没必要你再给我上节课了
I don't really need you to teach me a lesson.
你害怕了  是吧  鲍伯
You're afraid, aren't you, Bob?
没错
Uh-huh.
好吧  接受你的道歉
Well, I accept your apology.
那么我们就  就没事了
So we're... We're good?
哦  我真遗憾  鲍伯
Oh. I'm sorry, Bob.
木已成舟
Things are already in motion.
啥
Things?
啥样的事啊
Oh, come on. What kind of things?
真希望能助你一臂之力  可惜小女子我回天无力
I wish I could help you, but it's out of my hands.
你什么时候变成老爸了
When did you turn into dad?
变成老爸  变成老爸
Into dad? Into dad?
怎么搞的你脑袋里的想法老有回音
How come when you hear things in your head they always have an echo?
回音  回音
An echo? An echo?
我才没变成我老爸呢
I am not turning into dad.
只是我有很多责任
I just have a lot of responsibilities.
我要担心学校  工作  还有未来
School, a job, a future to worry about.
这些小子真不知道我多辛苦
Those kids have no idea how hard I work.
哦  伙计
Oh, man.
我真变成我老爸了
I am turning into dad.
嘿  伙计们
Hey, guys.
醒醒
Wake up.
-起来  -啥
- Get up. - What?
-现在是凌晨三点  -把鞋穿上
- It's three in the morning. - Get your shoes on.
咱们去找点乐子
We are going for a little trip.
我要让你们看看我仍然有趣
I'm gonna show you guys that I'm still fun,
孩子气  并且一点也不成熟
and childish and totally immature.
他回来了
He's back!
感觉如何
What do you think?
-下面该老妈了  -走
- Now let's get mom.  - Go.
我要是你的话就不那么做
Wouldn't do that if I were you.
还是别惹老妈了
Let's not get mom.
-嗨  邓肯夫人  -从我房间出去 洛根
- Hi, Mrs. Duncan.  - Get out of my bedroom, Logan.
不错  亲爱的
Okay, honey.
做得漂亮
Well done.
吸取教训了
Lesson learned.
你在说什么呢
What are you talking about?
这个  不是你的报复吗
This. Isn't this your revenge?
在你脸上涂鸦
Drawing on your face?
这像我的风格么  泰迪
Does that sound like me, Teddy?
不像  妈妈
It's doesn't, mom.
唔
Hmm.
这么说还有更多
So there's more?
还有
More?
还没开始呢
It hasn't even started.
哦
Oh.
泰迪  快把摄像机拿出来
Teddy, turn the camera on.
嘿  查莉  那个
Hey, Charlie. Well, uh,
其实我现在还没打算录制视频日记呢
I wasn't really planning on doing a video diary right now,
但老妈说让我打开摄像机  所以  要有什么事来了
but mom told me to turn the camera on, so something is up.
哦哦  甜甜圈
Ooh, donuts!
爆炸甜甜圈
Exploding donuts.
那真
That's...
教训吸取
Lesson learned.
-好了  咱们完事了吧  -哦
- Okay, are we done now?  - Oh.
是的
Yes.
第一阶段完事
With phase one.
哦  天啊
Oh, man.
祝我好运吧  小查莉
Wish me good luck, Charlie.
好了  PJ  我知道你不喜欢你妹妹有一段时间了
Okay, PJ. Now I know you've been resenting your sister for some time now.
所以我买了件能让你喜欢她的礼物
So I bought you something to help you finally get over it.
睁眼
Open your eyes.
-这是啥  -这是个洋娃娃泰迪
- What is it? - It's a Teddy doll.
来吧  扯一下弦
Go ahead. Pull the string.
你是最棒的大哥
You're the best big brother ever.
呀
Aw.
嘴太甜了
This is so sweet.
我很高兴你搬出去了
I'm so glad you moved out.
这话不那么甜了
That wasn't quite as nice.
我从没有真正喜欢过你
I never really liked you.
我是用塑料做的  但我仍比你聪明
I'm made of plastic and I'm still smarter than you.
这是最差劲的礼物了
This is the worst gift ever.
哦
Oh.
好了适可而止  我要把你退回商店
Okay that's it you're going back to the store.
你真漂亮  你是演员吗
You're beautiful. Are you an actress?
好吧  我再给你次机会
Okay, I'm going to give you one more shot.